


export const quiz = {

    totalQuestions: 20,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Question content 1 ?' ,
        answers: ['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Question content 2 ? ',
        answers: ['1', '2', '4', '5'],
        correctAnswer: '4',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Question content 3 ?',
        answers: ['Dubai', 'Algiers', ' :)','123'],
        correctAnswer: '123',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Question content 4 ?',
        answers: ['Den', 'Ma', 'Sep', 'we'],
        correctAnswer: 'MA',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Question content 5 ?',
        answers: ['g', 't', 'u', 'M'],
        correctAnswer: 't',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Question content 6 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Question content 7 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Question content 8 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Question content 9 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Question content 10 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Question content 11 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Question content 12 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: 'Question content 13 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Question content 14 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Question content 15 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: 'Question content 16 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 17,
        question: 'Question content 17 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 18,
        question: 'Question content 18 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 19,
        question: 'Question content 19 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
      {
        id: 20,
        question: 'Question content 20 ?',
        answers: ['','' ,'' ,''],
        correctAnswer: 'f',
      },
    ],
  };
  